(Raj:)So I read a study that
says a man with a dog
(Raj:)is three times more likely
to get a woman's phone number.
(Leonard:)Is it true even when
the man lets his dog
(Leonard:)lick peanut butter off his tongue?
(Raj:)I don't see why not.
(Howard:)If you're really desperate
to meet women
(Howard:)and like having food
eaten out of your mouth,
(Howard:)I could set you up with my mom.
(Sheldon:)Why is that funny?
(Sheldon:)That's just unhygienic.
(Leonard:)-It's a joke.
-I don't think so.
(Sheldon:)I believe that a joke
is a brief oral narrative
(Sheldon:)with a climactic humorous twist.
(Sheldon:)For example,
Wolowitz's mother is so fat
(Sheldon:)that she decided
to go on a diet,
(Sheldon:)or exercise, or both.
(Sheldon:)See? The twist is that people
don't usually change.
(Sheldon:)Well, they don't.